## Do Thi Vinh

#### MEDICAL COMMUNICATION SPECIALIST - HA NOI



✓ dovinh1126@gmail.com **\Circ** 0962.195.426 **\Circ** Chuong Duong Ward, Hoan Kiem District, Hanoi, VN

#### APPLICATION OBJECTIVE

Apply my own experiences and knowledge acquired at school to deal well with assigned work situations. This helps me to improve myself, improve my understanding, and learn more. The short-term goal is to master the work in the shortest possible time and the long-term goal is to advance to higher positions in the company.

#### **EDUCATION**

2013 - 2018

**Hanoi University of Pharmacy** • Specialized orientation: Clinical Pharmacy

GPA: 3.26/4 (very good grade)

### **Le Quy Don High School for the**Major: Physics **Gifted Students**

2010 - 2013

- GPA: Grade 10th: 8.6/10; Grade 11th: 8.3/10; Grade 12th: 8.0/10 (very good grade)

#### RESEARCH AND WORK EXPERIENCES

#### **Duc Giang General Hospital**

June 2017 - Mar 2018

#### Carry out my graduation thesis

- Mentor:
  - + Associate Professor Ph.D. Pham Thi Thuy Van
  - + M.S Hoang Thai Hoa
- Thesis title: Survey using asthma medication on outpatients in Duc Giang General Hospital
- Object: Survey of the characteristics of bronchial asthma patients, the selection and use of asthma medications in bronchial asthma outpatients aged 18 years or older based on the level of control and adherence at Duc Giang General Hospital

### PhD thesis of Nguyen Tu Son • Collaborator teacher

July 2017 - Dec 2017

- Imitating the asthma patient, go to pharmacies and buy drugs (Ventolin) and ask for advice from pharmacists at the pharmacy. Then complete the questionnaire according to the research topic.
- Giving gifts to the pharmacy and complete the questionnaire on asthma counseling at the pharmacy.
- Entering the data according to the instructions in the SPSS software

#### **Tutor**

2014 - 2018

#### Tutor for secondary school students

- Math tutoring for students in grades 8, Grade 9

#### **ACTIVITIES**

#### **Doctor and Friends Club**

Sep 2017 - Jul 2018

#### Volunteer for humanitarian volunteer programs

- Take part in volunteer trips in poor districts such as:
  - + "Tri ân mùa thu 2018-Lục Ngạn-Bắc Giang"
  - + "Hào khí Lam Kinh 2017-Thọ Xuân-Thanh Hóa"
  - + "Về miền quan họ 2017-Việt Yên-Bắc Giang"...
- Drug statistics.
- Classification of drugs by pharmacological group.
- Free distribution of drugs to poor people on prescriptions from doctors.

#### **Blood donation**

2014 - 2018

### Volunteer

- Participate in annual blood donation activities

# **Vietnam Young Physician Association**

July 2015 - Jan 2016

#### Volunteer

- Doing volunteer work at Bach Mai Hospital
- Helping patients and their family members move in the hospital quickly, conveniently
- Guide the patients using the services available in the hospital
- Remind patients and their family members to follow the rules in the hospital

#### **CERTIFICATIONS & AWARDS**

2018 Graduation type: very-good classification at Hanoi University of Pharmacy

2016 Achieved: Certificate of Merit of Vietnam Young Physician Association

#### **INTERESTS**

Participate in extracurricular activities, humanitarian volunteer programs Enjoy singing, listening to music and reading newspapers.

#### REFERENCES

Pham Thi Thuy Van Deputy head of clinical pharmacy department, Ha Noi University of

Pharmacy.

Email: Thuyvanemail@gmail.com

Mobile: 0904042232

Nguyen Duc Van

Manager of Doctor and Friends Club, Hung Viet Cancer Hospital

Email: nguyenvanbg@yahoo.com

Mobile: 0912211459

#### SKILLS

